

# Jingjing Hao, Scientist & Engineer

haojingjing.hjj@gmail.com

## **DETAILS**

0650258337

DRIVING LICENSE

Yes

#### LINKS

GitHub Home

**SKILLS** 

C/C++

Matlab

Python

# HOBBIES

Read, Dance VR games

LANGUAGES

English

French

Chinese

#### **PROFILE**

I am an engineer and an "undergraduate" scientist, but enjoys exploring world beside working with talented engineers and scientists. My primary attempts including sequenced RNA data twenty five years after Human Genome Project and encephalography data in the rise of brain research. And I also had leading experiences implementing including " (Intelligent) Electrical Appliances Control System" and "Online Shopping Platform" by working in teams while gainning my bachelor degree in 2010. And I had been delegates of MUN activities at Harbin, Beijing and Moscow, once winned a prize in Interdisciplinary Contest in modeling.

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Research Engineer PhD Position, Inria Saclay Ile-de-France

Oct 2017 - Present, Île-de-France

- Collected, analysed and visualised EEG data
- Learned basic PDE knowledge for fMRI

# Software Developer, Oracle

Jul 2014 - Apr 2017, Beijing

- Recruited as Oracle NCG 2014 and worked with System (hardware) teams
- Maintained and developed Solaris network driver
- Fixed several tricky kernel bugs

#### **EDUCATION**

# Tsinghua University, M.S. Control Science and Engineering

Sep 2011 – Jul 2014, Beijing

## Harbin Institute of Technology, B.S. Software Engineering

Sep 2019 - Jul 2011, Harbin

#### COURSES

### Professionalism, Coursera

Jan 2018 – Feb 2018

Business English Communication Skills Specialisation, Coursera

Jan 2017 - Jun 2017